// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who developed the JAVA programming Language",
    answer: "James Goslig",
    options: [
      "Wick Van Rossum",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf",
      "Guido Van Rossum",
      "James Goslig"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which type of programming does Python support?",
    answer: "Object-oriented programming",
    options: [
      "Object-oriented programming",
      "structured programming",
      "functional programming",
      "all of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is the corect extension of the java file?",
    answer: ".java",
    options: [
      ".js",
      ".java",
      ".jav",
      ".j"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Is JAVA code compiled or interpreted?",
    answer: "Both compiled and interpreted",
    options: [
      "Both compiled and interpreted",
      "JAVA code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
      "Only compiled",
      "Only interpreted"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the size of the int variable",
    answer: "32-bit",
    options: [
      "8-bit",
      "16-bit",
      "32-bit",
      "64-bit"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is the default value of the short variable",
    answer: "0.0",
    options: [
      "0.0",
      "0",
      "null",
      "undefined"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What kind of variables a class can consist of?",
    answer: "class variables, local variables, instance variables",
    options: [
      "class variables, instance variables",
      "class variables, local variables, instance variables",
      "class variables",
      "class variables, local variables"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "When static binding occurs?",
    answer: "Staic binding occurs during Compile time",
    options: [
      "Staic binding occurs during Compile time",
      "During load time",
      "During Runtime",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which operator is considered to be with highest precedence?",
    answer: "(), []",
    options: [
      "(), []",
      "-=",
      "-?",
      "-%"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is an immutable object?",
    answer: "An immutale object can't be changed once it is correct",
    options: [
      "An immutale object can be changed once it is correct",
      "An immutale object can't be changed once it is correct",
      "An immutable object is an instance of an abstract class",
      "None of the mentioned"
    ]
  },

];